resolving a confusing billing issue call
center
agent and
customer good afternoon thank you for
calling bright star Services my name is
Lisa how can I assist you today yeah hi
I'm hoping you can help me because I'm
really confused and frankly frustrated I
just got my bill and it's way higher
than usual I don't know what's going on
oh no I'm really sorry to hear that I
can imagine how frustrating that must be
let's get to the bottom of this together
could you please confirm your account
number or the phone number associated
with your account so I can pull up your
details sure it's 3 1 0 5 2 9 0
874 thank you for that I'm pulling up
your account now okay I've got it so you
mentioned that your bill is higher than
usual do you happen to know how much it
typically is and what the current amount
says yeah it's usually around $80 a
month but this time it's
$150 I don't know where all these extra
charges are coming from I see let's take
a closer look at the breakdown of this
month's bill so we can figure out what's
causing the increase I'll review the
charges line by line for you it'll just
take a moment okay that sounds good all
right I'm looking at your bill and it
looks like the standard charge for your
plan is still
$80 however I'm seeing a few additional
fees this month one of them is a late
payment fee from last month and there's
also a data overage charge have you
noticed any recent changes in your usage
like more streaming or data use hm well
I did go on a trip last month and used
my phone a bit more than usual but I
didn't think it would cost this much and
a late payment fee I didn't even know I
missed a payment how did that happen I
completely understand how that could be
surprising it looks like the late
payment fee was applied because your
payment last month was posted a few days
after the due date and as for the data
overage it seems like your plan has a
certain limit on data usage and you
exceeded that limit during your trip
that can definitely happen when we're
out and about using GPS streaming and so
on would you like me to go over your
current data plan and options in case
there's a more suitable plan that could
prevent these overage charges in the
future yeah that would be helpful but I
still don't get why I wasn't notified
about the late payment I usually stay on
top of those things I understand Mr
Garfield let me take a look at the
notifications we sent to you I see here
that a payment reminder was emailed to
you a few days before the due date but
sometimes those can end up in Spam
folders or get missed what I can do for
you is set up a text alert for future
bills that way you'll get a direct
notification on your phone as well as an
email would that be helpful yes that
would be great I don't always check my
email so a text alert would be much
better I'll set that up for you right
now you'll receive text reminders 3 days
before your due date going forward as
for the late payment fee I'd like to do
something to make this right for you
since it seems like this is a rare
occurrence on your account let me see if
I can wave that fee for you oh wow that
would be awesome I really appreciate it
not a problem at all you've been a loyal
customer for quite some time and I want
to make sure we take care of you let me
go ahead and remove that $25 late
payment fee done you'll see that
reflected on your next
statement awesome thanks for doing that
now about the data usage since you
mentioned that your usage was higher
than normal during your trip this might
have been a one-time thing however if
you think your data needs might increase
in the future I can review our current
plans with higher data limits to help
you avoid additional charges I
appreciate that but I don't think I'll
be using that much data again anytime
soon I didn't realize how much I was
using on my trip I think I'll stick with
my current plan for now that makes
sense I've put a note in your account
and we'll keep you on your current plan
if you ever find that your usage is
increasing feel free to reach out and
we'll make sure you have the right plan
to fit your needs Thank you Lisa you've
been really helpful you know I came into
this call frustrated but I feel a lot
better now I'm so glad to hear that Mr
Garfield it's always my goal to make
sure you leave the call with all your
concerns resolved is there anything else
I can assist you with today no that's it
thanks again for taking the time to
explain everything and for waving that
fee you've really helped turn this
around it was my pleasure I'm happy I
could help thank you for being a valued
customer and if you ever have any more
questions or need assistance don't
hesitate to reach out have a wonderful
day you too take care
thank you Mr Garfield goodbye if you
enjoyed this video give us a thumbs up
and remember to watch our other roleplay
videos
[Music]